

Date of birth
Nationality

Languages

15/02/2001

Vietnamese

Vietnamese

English

**Dutch** (learning)

# CONTACT

- **\** 0633461128
- ly.phamhoang@outlook.com
- Leidschendam, The Netherlands
- <u>lypham.super.site</u>

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Time Management

Communication

Critical thinking

Openness to Feedback

Creativity

**Empathy** 

Not afraid to face new challenges

# **HOANG TRUC LY PHAM**

# **UX DESIGNER**

With a solid foundation in research, prototyping, and UI design, I specialize in crafting engaging and intuitive applications and websites. I thrive on turning ideas into interactive, visually stunning realities, aiming to ensure that every project I undertake leaves a lasting impression.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Communication and Multimedia Design (User Experience Design)

09/2019 - 07/2023

De Haagse Hogeschool

Courses

- Research and Design
- Project Shared Spaces
- Project Smart Society
- Programming

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### KLM

02/2023 - 07/2023

**UX** Designer

- Research on a target group (students from HBO and WO).
- Design a prototype for the internship market application, which provides helpful information and guidance for the students who will join the internship market.
- Developed visuals elements for a pixel game.

#### Freelancer

03/2024 - NOW

• Designing advertisement pages for agencies & startups in Vietnam

### Primark

02/2024 - NOW

Part-time Sale Assistant

Help at the store & Giving advices to the customers

### **PROJECTS**

# The Platform Energy Transition - Gemeente Delft

09/2022 - 02/2023

UX Designer - Student

- Design UI elements and logo for the application.
- Come up with the concept that the resident's views can be collected to generate feedback and motivate neighbourhoods to take action to reduce the Carbon emissions.

# The Library Aanzet and Probiblio - Dordrecht 02/2022 - 05/2022 UX Designer - Student

- Research on a target group (children aged 8 12).
- Design a library concept that triggers the kid's imagination and gives them a feeling of home, relatedness, excitement and joy as they immerse themselves in a new world of books.
- Create a floor map for the library and scale model.

# **HOBBIES**

- · Cycling, skating
- Learning programming languages
- Boardgames
- DIY things
- Arts

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

### Research and Data Analysis

- A/B Testing
- Usability Testing
- Proficient in using tools for data analysis [SurveyMonkey, Heat-map Tools, Google Analytics]

### **Design Tools**

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Balsamiq
- Webflow

### Front-end Development

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript

#### Microsoft Office Suit

- Word
- Excel
- PowerPoint

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Looking to obtain a position where I can apply my relevant coursework and passion for design to create a stimulating and attractive design for users. Additionally, I aim to enhance my skills in prototyping and visualizations while further developing myself professionally.

# **PROTFOLIO**

<u>Visit my portfolio</u> (lypham.super.site) to explore my work and design projects.